My name is Berser and I'm a special utility of three for all of the 6-2.
I'm going to ask you need me to start from the first question.
Chair, Chair Johnson to give the invitation.
Thank you, sir.
I'd rather than having me thank you so much for this community that we live in and
Lord just feel blessed to be a part of it.
I thank you for those in this room that
Lord represents so much hard work, so much passion and care for our community trying to make it the best that it can be.
And Lord for their work.
I pray that you just bless their families and Lord bless the time.
Here this evening I pray that you would grant the wisdom.
Lord, that you would just be with each decision that's made.
And Lord, again, pray for your blessing on each of these that are here.
And Lord is grateful to be blessed and a part of this community as these people help make it that way.
And we just pray that you would guide the next few moments.
And that you would be honored in this place.
It's in Jesus name we pray.
Amen.
Thank you.
I pray.
Ask, pray.
God bless.
Massage.
Amen.
He's healed.
And thank you.
asked that we mutually agreed to terminate the contract due to, he has multiple accounts.
He's really, really busy.
He just feels that it'd be best if we go out.
Because he's been having a hard time catching that.
We've had tons of properties. He's a one-man show.
He's worked by himself.
And he feels that he, he, he, he, his contract is indeed for another year,
but he feels that it earlier is a better.
So we can, it's going to put us a little behind, but in longer and I believe,
it's going to help us out so we can go out.
bid as soon as basically emergency the bid. We don't have to give them the 30 days that
is contract initially states that we got to give them 30 days to when we terminate the
contract. So now we can just immediately go out once this is a proven. He has signed the
termination mutual termination agreement. He's signed it last time.
So once we terminate it, it's factory immediately. That's what you're saying. Yes, it once
it's terminate. We can go out tomorrow. We can instantly.
It's not only can we go out tomorrow. We will be going. Yeah, we will. We will. We won't
go out tomorrow. Since it's under 25,000 or under 50,000, we don't have to go out for
formal bid. We just got to give them yet three. Three quotes. Right now, a lot of our
crews, we've had people from part cemetery and all that, trying to help out very much. It
is a cost of over time in some cases. We also do know that there are some other people in the
community that would really like to be interested in having a bid. So if we can get out
of those contract quickly, get some other people in place, we can start hitting some of the
high weeds that you see when you drive around town. So there's our nerdy as an interest in.
Yeah, we have probably three or four people that are interested in town and a few out of town.
Like I said, we have cemetery parks, some of the right way guys, the directors have been
gracious enough to lend them to us and help us on the so-called downtime if they have.
You know, I'm glad I'm going to go through Friday. We'll be at the LBF good for it. So I take
out the high weeds along a street along a good rich bulldozer. Yeah, they, they, if you go by the
east side isn't finished because it was really wet and they were getting stuck. So they, it was
taking them more time than it's sort of so they just kind of stopped into what it would go
to dry out and pick it up in this Friday. So I would definitely like to get into the contract
on the word, but this is the best way to do that. Okay. And if I'm correct, this is just for the
appointment because I believe hogbing also still does our cemetery. Just for the payments. Yes.
And how many of you feel were behind? How many locations are you? I would say, I would say
30 or 40. I mean, there's, I got several of the payment work orders today. So they're just,
we just got to get this going on. And again, I call him in and he, we both agreed. You know, he said
about what I want to hold you guys up, but I just got too much going on, like I said, he's one man
job. So he just feels like he, uh, needs to let it go and keep us from being held up.
It's falling farther behind. Yeah. But I got to respect because, you know, the contract initially
said, we have to give him 30 days, but he agreed.
termination is possible.
Yep.
Yeah, motion to occur.
Make a motion that we accept the mutual termination agreement
with Hopping's Laws Service for the Baitment Work.
Second.
Lewis.
Aye.
Forster.
Judson.
Aye.
Thank you.
I don't need a discussion.
Go through climate closure research and recommendation.
Jill.
I think Jill just maybe just a very quick summary
for those that might be tweeting in.
We just took a tour of our new customer service area in the reasoning for this.
And we do recognize that this is a decision that you may be getting some calls about,
but it really is something that we believe is going to be making us a more efficient operation
and also providing better customer service.
So let's start with a drive through itself.
The only business that can be conducted in the drive through is a payment.
If our customer needs to do anything else to their account,
change a name, close the account, anything else we ask them to come in.
So the only thing that we do is take payments in our drive through.
We actually closed the drive through for the remodel May 25th.
Prior to that, about a week prior,
the council did approve a contract with Welch State Bank to begin taking payments through their drive
through and at their office facilities.
Prior to that, we started distributing surveys out to each customer.
And we would tell them what we're getting ready to do with the remodel and that,
and the survey actually says, we're looking at possibly permanently closing the drive through.
If you have any input, please give it to us.
We received 16 of those surveys back.
Each time we added a bank onto that, we would change the survey to add that they could go pay it,
those banks.
So the surveys changed a little bit.
But we always asked in the same thing just for input on closing the drive through.
We got 16 back.
We also had, I had an email exchange with a co-worker here at the city.
And once he realized that we are giving other drive through options, he understood.
We also had a little bit of a Facebook exchange.
So one of the things that was a concern was the due dates.
We don't treat anybody if they pay at the bank or they pay at our facility.
We don't treat them any differently in regards to due dates.
By ordinance, your due date is printed on your bill and you have to pay that day or before.
So if your bill is due on the second and you come into the bank or to our facility on the second,
you don't get any penalties.
If you come into either one of those on the third, you will get a penalty.
So we don't treat anybody differently.
That was something we wanted to make sure and get across to the public.
I personally heard it because our customer service area was literally right across in a small hallway right across from my office.
And I got to hear them actually talk to the people and hand out the surveys and I often heard
people once they realize they had other options, well,
and security and first national to go through their drive
through something else to point out, there's two other
things credit card payments. Those banks will take credit
cards for payment. Here at the city face to face, we cannot do
that. Our credit card fees would be very high and we can't
forward right now to do it. We look at it every couple of
years for sure to see because we really want to be able to
do that. It's just very expensive and credit card fees. The
other thing is we had prior to the remodel, we had one
office, here at the Civic Center, and we had one drive
through. Now with the banks included, we have eight offices
including the Civic Center and six drive throughs, which is just
the three banks, but they have multiple lengths. So they're
going to get service faster. They do need to bring their
bill in. It will be stamped and they'll get to keep a half,
keep half and the bank keeps half. If they only bring a portion of
their bill in, the bank will keep that portion and give them a
receipt for their payment. We are going to expand the services in
that department. We're bringing other public services to that
department and we wouldn't do a lot of detail during the tour. So if
you guys have any questions, I'd love to answer them.
I'm not a curiosity if I know sometimes banks have more holidays
and probably the city does. What if there's a due date? I mean, it's on
Monday. What happens if they're like? If they're not open,
you need the banks aren't open and we are open, then they'll need to bring it
here. If their due date is that Monday, they'll need to make sure we get it.
We have two drop boxes that could drive through and drop it in the drop box
and they would not get a penalty if it got in that day,
and then or they could come in. But there's always a drive through option at
least through a drop box with us.
Yeah, I'll pay also. Yes. Yes. Automate pay through your bank.
Yeah. Yeah. Do they need to come in here to set that up or can they do that at the bank?
They need to come in here. Any other business besides making a payment needs to happen here.
Okay. Yeah. I usually use the drive through, but is it back open? No.
We wanted to talk with you about a get through plan on opening and we don't plan on opening.
Yeah.
It's all right.
Okay.
Well, that's just a discussion item.
I think if you're ultimately, that's the city manager and deans and staff's decision,
I would certainly support it. We just wanted to make you aware of it
and make you aware of what we've tried to do. It's not just a uniform decision
to close that we've tried to bump up the services that we're making to everybody else.
And it also ties into what we're trying to do with a broader customer service area where we're
more efficient with our personnel.
Why do you need to be aware of that?
There we go.
Thank you, Jim. Thanks.
I don't have a way of knowing the business being, isn't it?
Not on this, okay?
Stafford ports.
I can tell you.
By guy quasi per style.
Come on.
Trust me, you can need announcements.
Nothing.
A gentleman.
You.
Looks like you're in.
I'll second.
No, sorry.
Listen.
Aye.
Forster.
Lewis.
Aye.